Guide to the Jennings Photograph Collection [1858]-1957 PR 135
New-York Historical Society
- Series V: Jennings Family
  - Oversize Group Portraits
    - Harlem Hospital staff, 1914-1916 (Offsite-box 12, Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Wesleyan University, 1903 (Offsite-box 12, Box 13, Folder 67)
    - Unidentified groups, [1903-1915] (Offsite-box 12, Box 13, Folder 68)
- Oversize Material
  - From Series III
    - Washington Heights view, undated (Offsite-box 12, Box 13, Folder 69)
  - From Series V
    - Allen family residence, Meriden, CT, undated (Offsite-box 12, Box 13, Folder 70)